<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

	<string name="description_wifi">
		timestamp BSSID SSID frequency(MHz) level(dBm) capabilities\n
		Capabilities describes the authentication, key management, and encryption schemes supported by the access point.
	</string>

	<string name="description_accelerometer">
		timestamp x y z\n
		All values are in SI units (m/s^2)
	</string>

	<string name="description_gyroscope_uncalibrated">
		timestamp x y z estimated-drift-x estimated-drift-y estimated-drift-z\n
		All values are in radians/second\n
		Factory calibration and temperature compensation is still applied to the rate of rotation (angular speeds).
	</string>

	<string name="description_magnetometer_uncalibrated">
		timestamp x y z estimated-bias-x estimated-bias-y estimated-bias-z\n
		All values are in micro-Tesla (uT)\n
		Factory calibration and temperature compensation are applied to this measurement
	</string>

	<string name="description_gyroscope">
		timestamp x y z\n
		All values are in radians/second
	</string>

	<string name="description_magnetometer">
		timestamp x y z\n
		All values are in micro-Tesla (uT)
	</string>

	<string name="description_game_rotation_vector">
		timestamp x*sin(&#952;/2) y*sin(&#952;/2) z*sin(&#952;/2) [cos(&#952;/2)] [estimated-heading-accuracy(radians)]\n
		Identical to rotation-vector except that it doesn\'t use the geomagnetic field.
		Therefore the Y axis doesn\'t point north, but instead to some other reference.
	</string>

	<string name="description_geomagnetic_rotation_vector">
		timestamp x*sin(&#952;/2) y*sin(&#952;/2) z*sin(&#952;/2) [cos(&#952;/2)]\n
		Similar to rotation-vector, but using a magnetometer instead of using a gyroscope.
	</string>

	<string name="description_gravity">
		timestamp x y z\n
		All values are in SI units (m/s^2)\n
		A three dimensional vector indicating the direction and magnitude of gravity.
	</string>

	<string name="description_linear_acceleration">
		timestamp x y z\n
		All values are in SI units (m/s^2)
	</string>

	<string name="description_rotation_vector">
		timestamp x*sin(&#952;/2) y*sin(&#952;/2) z*sin(&#952;/2) [cos(&#952;/2)] [estimated-heading-accuracy(radians)]\n
		The rotation vector represents the orientation of the device as a combination of
		an angle and an axis, in which the device has rotated through an angle &#952; around
		an axis &#60;x, y, z&#62;.\n\n
		The reference coordinate system is defined as a direct orthonormal basis, where:\n
		- X is defined as the vector product Y.Z (It is tangential to the ground at the device\'s current location and roughly points East).\n
		- Y is tangential to the ground at the device\'s current location and points towards magnetic north.\n
		- Z points towards the sky and is perpendicular to the ground.
	</string>

	<string name="description_significant_motion">
		timestamp
		It triggers when an event occurs and then automatically disables itself.
	</string>

	<string name="description_step_counter">
		timestamp
		A sensor of this type returns the number of steps taken by the user since the last reboot while activated.
	</string>

	<string name="description_step_detector">
		timestamp
		A sensor of this type triggers an event each time a step is taken by the
		user. The only allowed value to return is 1.0 and an event is generated
		for each step. Like with any other event, the timestamp indicates when
		the event (here the step) occurred, this corresponds to when the foot
		hit the ground, generating a high variation in acceleration.
	</string>

	<string name="description_ambient_temperature">
		timestamp temperature(degree)
		Ambient (room) temperature in degree Celsius.
	</string>

	<string name="description_light">
		timestamp light(lux)
		Ambient light level in SI lux units.
	</string>

	<string name="description_pressure">
		timestamp pressure(hPa)
		Atmospheric pressure in hPa (millibar).
	</string>

	<string name="description_relative_humidity">
		timestamp humidity(%)
		Relative ambient air humidity in percent.
	</string>

	<string name="description_heart_rate">
		timestamp heart-rate
		A constant describing a heart rate monitor.\n
		The reported value is the heart rate in beats per minute.
	</string>

	<string name="description_proximity">
		timestamp proximity (in centimeters) [unknown] [unknown]
		Proximity sensor distance measured in centimeters.\n
		Note: Some proximity sensors only support a binary near or far measurement.
		In this case, the sensor should report its maximum range value in the far
		state and a lesser value in the near state.
	</string>

	<string name="description_unknown">
		Sorry, there is no description for this sensor.
	</string>

	<string name="description_location_passive">
		timestamp latitude(degrees) longitude(degrees) altitude(meters) bearing(degrees) accuracy(meters) speed(meters/second)\n
		This provider can be used to passively receive location updates when other applications or
		services request them without actually requesting the locations yourself.
	</string>

	<string name="description_location_gps">
		timestamp latitude(degrees) longitude(degrees) altitude(meters) bearing(degrees) accuracy(meters) speed(meters/second)\n
		This provider determines location using satellites. Depending on conditions, this provider
		may take a while to return a location fix..
	</string>

	<string name="description_location_wifi_and_cells">
		timestamp latitude(degrees) longitude(degrees) altitude(meters) bearing(degrees) accuracy(meters) speed(meters/second)\n
		This provider determines location based on availability of cell tower and WiFi access points.
		Results are retrieved by means of a network lookup.
	</string>

	<string name="description_bluetooth">
		timestamp mac-address rssi(dBm) data
	</string>

	<string name="description_nmea">
		timestamp sentence
		NMEA sentences from the GPS.\n
		NMEA 0183 is a standard for communicating with marine electronic devices and
		is a common method for receiving data from a GPS, typically over a serial port.
	</string>

	<string name="description_nfc">
		timestamp
	</string>

	<string name="description_position_references">
		timestamp id name
		Reference position clicked.
	</string>
</resources>